<application>
  <component name="AppStorage">
    <histories>
      <item value="Repodata is over 2 weeks old. Install yum-cron? Or run: yum makecache fast" />
      <item value="Adds option to disable auto-popup completions on a space to leave your already typed text as you intended. Configure it in Editor &gt; General &gt; Code Completion settings (Preferences on OS X). Disable for all languages or only for languages in a configurable list. If you want to insert a suggestion for space disabled auto-pop then either use TAB or ENTER or manually change the selected suggestion before using SPACE to insert it. Prompted by delayed auto-popup completions in Kotlin after typing var, val or null followed by a space, inserting some random function, triggering a severe bout of Tourette’s as a result." />
      <item value="Adds option to disable auto-popup completions on a space to leave your already typed text as you intended.&#10;Configure it in Editor &gt; General &gt; Code Completion settings (Preferences on OS X). Disable for all languages or only for languages in a configurable list.&#10;If you want to insert a suggestion for space disabled auto-pop then either use TAB or ENTER or manually change the selected suggestion before using SPACE to insert it.&#10;Prompted by delayed auto-popup completions in Kotlin after typing var, val or null followed by a space, inserting some random function, triggering a severe bout of Tourette’s as a result." />
      <item value="A universally unique identifier (UUID) generator. For example : 123e4567-e89b-12d3-a456-426655440000. You will find it in the Generate popup -&gt; Random UUID. Available actions : Random UUID Generate UUID to clipboard Generate UUID Popup Toggle UUID dashes" />
      <item value="A universally unique identifier (UUID) generator. For example : 123e4567-e89b-12d3-a456-426655440000. You will find it in the Generate popup -&gt; Random UUID. Available actions :&#10;Random UUID&#10;Generate UUID to clipboard&#10;Generate UUID Popup&#10;Toggle UUID dashes" />
      <item value="Insert random data with the press of a single key. Adds actions to insert random data into your editor, which can be useful when writing tests." />
      <item value="A collection of color themes created by Dayle Rees for all JetBrains platforms." />
      <item value="Open your Angular or AngularJS project. Make sure that you have AngularJS or Angular library files in your project (for example, in the node_modules folder) – this is required for the IDE to enable Angular support for this project. Now, you will get Angular-specific code completion, navigation, and many other features." />
      <item value="Open your Angular or AngularJS project.&#10;Make sure that you have AngularJS or Angular library files in your project (for example, in the node_modules folder) – this is required for the IDE to enable Angular support for this project.&#10;Now, you will get Angular-specific code completion, navigation, and many other features." />
      <item value="IntelliJ Lombok plugin GitHub | Issues | Donate ( PayPal ) A plugin that adds first-class support for Project Lombok Sponsors Discuss, review, and share code with your team in your JetBrains IDE. Integrates with Slack, Jira, Trello, Github and more. Try it free! Features" />
      <item value="Support for Node.js projects. Features Run Node.js applications from the IDE and debug them using the built-in visual debugger Profile Node.js applications from the IDE Attach debugger to the running Node.js process Run and debug Mocha tests right in the IDE Create new Express projects from the IDE Welcome screen You can also run and debug Node.js applications in the remote environments such as Docker containers, Vagrant machines and remote servers right from the IDE. For that, please install the Node.js remote interpreters plugin. Here you can find more information on working with Node.js in the IDE." />
      <item value="Support for Node.js projects.&#10;Features&#10;Run Node.js applications from the IDE and debug them using the built-in visual debugger&#10;Profile Node.js applications from the IDE&#10;Attach debugger to the running Node.js process&#10;Run and debug Mocha tests right in the IDE&#10;Create new Express projects from the IDE Welcome screen&#10;You can also run and debug Node.js applications in the remote environments such as Docker containers, Vagrant machines and remote servers right from the IDE. For that, please install the Node.js remote interpreters plugin.&#10;Here you can find more information on working with Node.js in the IDE." />
      <item value="The Table Editor is a newly introduced feature of CSV Plugin v2.*. Support its ongoing development by reporting issues, providing suggestions, contributing ideas/features or by just giving it a thumbs up. Lightweight CSV plugin that supports editing files in CSV/TSV format. Features: CSV/TSV/PSV file detection table editor customizable text editor syntax validation syntax highlighting (configurable) content formatting (configurable) quick fix inspections intentions (Alt+Enter), e.g. Quote/Unquote (all), Shift Column Left/Right structure view (header-entry layout) support for ',', ';', '|' or '↹' as value separator highlight of active column values customizable column coloring tab (↹) separator highlighting TSV file support: TSV files are recognized as such but treated as a variant of CSV files, the same syntax highlighting and code style settings are applied. Code formatting: Default code formatting is 'Tabularize'. Can be changed in Settings -&gt; Editor -&gt; Code Style -&gt; CSV For more detailed information please have a look at the README. Thanks to @royqh1979, @egoisticalgoat, @sabi0, @ptahchiev, @ghost, @MarkJeronimus and others for supporting me and the project! IntelliJ IDEA Ultimate/PhpStorm/DataGrip/etc.: The plugin is fully compatible with the 'Edit as Table...' functionality. In IDE releases prior v2017.3, the shortcut in the editor context menu becomes invisible when using this plugin. However, the option can still be accessed via Toolbar -&gt; Edit -&gt; 'Edit as Table...'." />
      <item value="The Table Editor is a newly introduced feature of CSV Plugin v2.*. Support its ongoing development by reporting issues, providing suggestions, contributing ideas/features or by just giving it a thumbs up. Lightweight CSV plugin that supports editing files in CSV/TSV format. Features: CSV/TSV/PSV file detection&#10;table editor&#10;customizable text editor&#10;syntax validation&#10;syntax highlighting (configurable)&#10;content formatting (configurable)&#10;quick fix inspections&#10;intentions (Alt+Enter), e.g. Quote/Unquote (all), Shift Column Left/Right&#10;structure view (header-entry layout)&#10;support for ',', ';', '|' or '↹' as value separator&#10;highlight of active column values&#10;customizable column coloring&#10;tab (↹) separator highlighting&#10;TSV file support: TSV files are recognized as such but treated as a variant of CSV files, the same syntax highlighting and code style settings are applied. Code formatting: Default code formatting is 'Tabularize'. Can be changed in Settings -&gt; Editor -&gt; Code Style -&gt; CSV For more detailed information please have a look at the README. Thanks to @royqh1979, @egoisticalgoat, @sabi0, @ptahchiev, @ghost, @MarkJeronimus and others for supporting me and the project! IntelliJ IDEA Ultimate/PhpStorm/DataGrip/etc.: The plugin is fully compatible with the 'Edit as Table...' functionality. In IDE releases prior v2017.3, the shortcut in the editor context menu becomes invisible when using this plugin. However, the option can still be accessed via Toolbar -&gt; Edit -&gt; 'Edit as Table...'." />
      <item value="Bash language support for the IntelliJ platform. Supports run configurations, syntax highlighting, rename refactoring, documentation lookup, inspections, quickfixes and much more. Do you like it? Give it a star at GitHub. Rate it at plugins.jetbrains.com. News for users of 2019.2: JetBrains is bundling a new Shell plugin with 2019.2. You shouldn't use BashSupport and Shell simultaneously. Make sure to disable one of them. BashSupport supports more advanced features. Shell is more robust and providing better integration of basic functionality. BashSupport's future: Visit bashsupport.com to learn more about this. In short: BashSupport will remain available, free, and open-source. Thanks for being part of BashSupport! It's more than 10 years now and the most popular community plugin. It's far from perfect - thanks for using it nevertheless! JetBrain's Shell plugin is likely to become the new default for developers of shell scripts. This means that there's no future for BashSupport here. Development will be limited to maintenance and fixes for serious issues. Most likely there will be a new, paid BashSupport Pro plugin in the future. It will add missing functionality on top of the JetBrains plugin." />
      <item value="Bash language support for the IntelliJ platform. Supports run configurations, syntax highlighting, rename refactoring, documentation lookup, inspections, quickfixes and much more. Do you like it? Give it a star at GitHub. Rate it at plugins.jetbrains.com. News for users of 2019.2: JetBrains is bundling a new Shell plugin with 2019.2. You shouldn't use BashSupport and Shell simultaneously. Make sure to disable one of them. BashSupport supports more advanced features. Shell is more robust and providing better integration of basic functionality. BashSupport's future: Visit bashsupport.com to learn more about this. In short:&#10;BashSupport will remain available, free, and open-source.&#10;Thanks for being part of BashSupport! It's more than 10 years now and the most popular community plugin. It's far from perfect - thanks for using it nevertheless!&#10;JetBrain's Shell plugin is likely to become the new default for developers of shell scripts. This means that there's no future for BashSupport here.&#10;Development will be limited to maintenance and fixes for serious issues.&#10;Most likely there will be a new, paid BashSupport Pro plugin in the future. It will add missing functionality on top of the JetBrains plugin." />
      <item value="Lets you download and build Docker images, create and start Docker containers, and carry out other related tasks. Documentation" />
      <item value="Sponsors Discuss, review, and share code with your team in your JetBrains IDE. Integrates with Slack, Jira, Trello, Github and more. Try it free! Features" />
      <item value="A plugin that adds first-class support for Project Lombok" />
      <item value="Shows project statistic. This plugin shows files sorted by their extension along with size, line count LOC etc. User can select (Project/Module/Package/File) scope using the 'Refresh on selection' button. (This plugin requires Java 1.8)" />
      <item value="The function of this product is to count the number of lines of code, the number of lines of comment, the number of blank lines, the number and location of each file function, the number of file types and the update time" />
      <item value="VS Code Keymap for IntelliJ-based IDEs: IntelliJ IDEA, WebStorm, PhpStorm, and others&#10;Change Notes&#10;Fixed TAB in editor&#10;Fixed shortcut for Close Content action" />
      <item value="Configure automatic updates." />
      <item value="You can also find the details about our release, in the release notes." />
      <item value="And many more features, like preserving cookies between HTTP requests, improved debugging, and variable refactoring experiences: learn about the new version on our website" />
      <item value="Jupyter Notebook Integration has been improved. Run all cells with a single button click, select and configure your Jupyter server, keep track of variables while debugging them, restart the kernel and publish notebooks to JetBrains Datalore.&#10;Syntax highlight support for many other languages has been added. Highlight the syntax of Windows .bat files, C#, C++, Groovy, Lua, Makefiles, and more.&#10;Support for some major Python 3.8 features. Try out positional-only parameters, variable assignment within expressions, 'Final' qualifier, and new ways to use f-strings to present values and variables.&#10;cURL format is now supported for HTTP requests. Copy your cURL formatted request and paste it directly into your HTTP Request file for it to be converted into its format, and then feel free to modify the request's parameters, headers, or body." />
      <item value="New in PyCharm: Jupyter Notebook Integration has been improved. Run all cells with a single button click, select and configure your Jupyter server, keep track of variables while debugging them, restart the kernel and publish notebooks to JetBrains Datalore. Syntax highlight support for many other languages has been added. Highlight the syntax of Windows .bat files, C#, C++, Groovy, Lua, Makefiles, and more. Support for some major Python 3.8 features. Try out positional-only parameters, variable assignment within expressions, 'Final' qualifier, and new ways to use f-strings to present values and variables. cURL format is now supported for HTTP requests. Copy your cURL formatted request and paste it directly into your HTTP Request file for it to be converted into its format, and then feel free to modify the request's parameters, headers, or body. And many more features, like preserving cookies between HTTP requests, improved debugging, and variable refactoring experiences: learn about the new version on our website You can also find the details about our release, in the release notes." />
      <item value="New in PyCharm:&#10;Jupyter Notebook Integration has been improved. Run all cells with a single button click, select and configure your Jupyter server, keep track of variables while debugging them, restart the kernel and publish notebooks to JetBrains Datalore.&#10;Syntax highlight support for many other languages has been added. Highlight the syntax of Windows .bat files, C#, C++, Groovy, Lua, Makefiles, and more.&#10;Support for some major Python 3.8 features. Try out positional-only parameters, variable assignment within expressions, 'Final' qualifier, and new ways to use f-strings to present values and variables.&#10;cURL format is now supported for HTTP requests. Copy your cURL formatted request and paste it directly into your HTTP Request file for it to be converted into its format, and then feel free to modify the request's parameters, headers, or body.&#10;And many more features, like preserving cookies between HTTP requests, improved debugging, and variable refactoring experiences: learn about the new version on our website&#10;You can also find the details about our release, in the release notes." />
      <item value="Since its first release, the Key Promoter X had more than 200.000 downloads. It is top-rated on the JetBrains site, and since it is entirely open-source, other plugin developers can browse through the code to understand how things are implemented. The plugin is not for me or a byproduct of something I would do anyway. It is for you who want to learn shortcuts in IntelliJ IDEA, and I give away some of my free time to keep it up to date and fix bugs. If you appreciate my efforts, then please donate some money. Latest changes &quot;Do not show again&quot; action dismisses the tip immediately (Issue 34) Increase possible settings for notification limits (Issue 30) Add plugin icon shown in the settings and the repository New icons that better integrate into the UI Implemented a setting to only show &quot;Keyboard&quot; shortcuts. This is default and can be adjusted. Fixed exception that occurred on closing Keymap dialog in 2018.3. Removed setting for maximum visible notifications. IDEA 2018.3 seems to restrict this itself. Implemented feature-request: Minimum count before notification Fixed empty tool-window with several windows open This message will only appear once for each new version. The donation link can later be found in the plugin description under Settings | Plugins | Key Promoter X." />
      <item value="Since its first release, the Key Promoter X had more than 200.000 downloads. It is top-rated on the JetBrains site, and since it is entirely open-source, other plugin developers can browse through the code to understand how things are implemented.&#10;The plugin is not for me or a byproduct of something I would do anyway. It is for you who want to learn shortcuts in IntelliJ IDEA, and I give away some of my free time to keep it up to date and fix bugs. If you appreciate my efforts, then please donate some money.&#10;Latest changes&#10;&quot;Do not show again&quot; action dismisses the tip immediately (Issue 34)&#10;Increase possible settings for notification limits (Issue 30)&#10;Add plugin icon shown in the settings and the repository&#10;New icons that better integrate into the UI&#10;Implemented a setting to only show &quot;Keyboard&quot; shortcuts. This is default and can be adjusted.&#10;Fixed exception that occurred on closing Keymap dialog in 2018.3.&#10;Removed setting for maximum visible notifications. IDEA 2018.3 seems to restrict this itself.&#10;Implemented feature-request: Minimum count before notification&#10;Fixed empty tool-window with several windows open This message will only appear once for each new version. The donation link can later be found in the plugin description under Settings | Plugins | Key Promoter X." />
      <item value="Eclipse Keymap for IntelliJ-based IDEs: IntelliJ IDEA, WebStorm, PhpStorm, Rider, Android Studio, and others. Use this plugin if the Eclipse keymap is not pre-installed in your IDE." />
      <item value="Generating Kotlin data class from any legal JSON string or any URLs that returns a JSON string as response Generating Kotlin data class from any legal JSON text when right click on directory and select New -&gt; Kotlin data class File from JSON Supporting (almostly) all kinds of JSON libs' annotation(Gson, Jackson, Fastjson, MoShi and LoganSquare, kotlinx.serialization(default custom value)) Customizing your own annotations Initializing properties with default values Allowing properties to be nullable(?) Determining property nullability automatically Renaming property names to be camelCase style when selecting a target JSON lib annotation． Generating Kotlin data class as individual classes Generating Kotlin data class as inner classes Formatting any legal JSON string Generating Map Type when json key is primiti" />
      <item value="The Key Promoter X helps you to learn essential shortcuts while you are working. When you use the mouse on a button inside the IDE, the Key Promoter X shows you the keyboard shortcut that you should have used instead. This provides an easy way to learn how to replace tedious mouse work with keyboard keys and helps to transition to a faster, mouse free development. Currently, it supports toolbar buttons, menu buttons, tool windows and the actions therein. The Key Promoter X tool window shows you a hit-list of the mouse actions you use the most and directly provides you with the shortcut you can use instead. For buttons that don't have a shortcut, the Key Promoter X prompts you with the possibility to directly create one. Dmitry Kashin had the original idea for a &quot;Key Promoters&quot; but used custom UI elements which often clashed with the IntelliJ IDEA UI. Key Promoter X is a completely rewritten version of the original idea and removes the custom pop-up window with IntelliJ internal message balloons. It, therefore, integrates much better into the IDE, fixes glitches and provides a more non-disruptive way of learning shortcut bindings." />
      <item value="Part" />
      <item value="Brokenpipe " />
      <item value="BrokenPipeError:[Errno32]Brokenpipe " />
      <item value=" was not found" />
      <item value="fatal: unable to access 'https://github.com/streamlink/streamlink/': Network file descriptor is not connected " />
      <item value="tringindicesmustbeintegers" />
      <item value="Type Error:stringindicesmustbeintegers" />
      <item value="classification" />
      <item value="getstatusoutput" />
      <item value="Return (exitcode, output) of executing cmd in a shell. Execute the string 'cmd' in a shell with 'check_output' and return a 2-tuple (status, output). The locale encoding is used to decode the output and process newlines. A trailing newline is stripped from the output. The exit status for the command can be interpreted according to the rules for the function 'wait'. Example: &gt;&gt;&gt; import subprocess &gt;&gt;&gt; subprocess.getstatusoutput('ls /bin/ls') (0, '/bin/ls') &gt;&gt;&gt; subprocess.getstatusoutput('cat /bin/junk') (1, 'cat: /bin/junk: No such file or directory') &gt;&gt;&gt; subprocess.getstatusoutput('/bin/junk') (127, 'sh: /bin/junk: not found') &gt;&gt;&gt; subprocess.getstatusoutput('/bin/kill $$') (-15, '')" />
      <item value="worst" />
      <item value="Message: stale element reference: element is not attached to the page document" />
      <item value="发布任务" />
      <item value="发布" />
      <item value="ASSOCIATION" />
      <item value="LIVE_ASSOCIATION_TABLE" />
      <item value="association" />
    </histories>
    <option name="languageScores">
      <map>
        <entry key="CHINESE" value="517" />
        <entry key="ENGLISH" value="517" />
        <entry key="DANISH" value="2" />
        <entry key="GERMAN" value="1" />
        <entry key="FRENCH" value="2" />
        <entry key="HAITIAN_CREOLE" value="3" />
        <entry key="CORSICAN" value="1" />
        <entry key="ROMANIAN" value="2" />
        <entry key="PORTUGUESE" value="1" />
        <entry key="SWEDISH" value="6" />
        <entry key="TELUGU" value="1" />
        <entry key="TURKISH" value="1" />
        <entry key="SPANISH" value="2" />
        <entry key="HUNGARIAN" value="1" />
        <entry key="ITALIAN" value="4" />
        <entry key="HINDI" value="3" />
      </map>
    </option>
  </component>
  <component name="Settings">
    <option name="baiduTranslateSettings">
      <app-key>
        <option name="appId" value="20180726000189099" />
        <option name="appKeyConfigured" value="true" />
      </app-key>
    </option>
    <option name="googleTranslateSettings">
      <google-translate>
        <option name="useTranslateGoogleCom" value="true" />
      </google-translate>
    </option>
    <option name="ignoreRegExp" value="" />
    <option name="translator" value="fanyi.baidu" />
  </component>
</application>